No laughing!
I hate children!
Freddie, you know
this school has a strict rule
against turning your locker
into a time machine.
It's a surveillance system.
For?
Someone snuck
into my locker yesterday
and stole
my fruit-scented markers.
So the next time
someone breaks in,
it'll trigger this mechanism
which causes this camera
to snap a picture of the thief,
so I'll know that
you took my markers.
Sorry. I forgot to tell you.
How'd you pick my lock? Sam.
Sam.
Of course.
Hey, where's the tangerine one?
I'm not sure.
Hmm.
So what did you need
the markers for?
To make that poster.
Oh, yeah.
"'ICarly' 50th web show
spectacular."
Cool. Spreading the word.
And the smell of fruits.
There. It's up.
Can you believe
we're about to shoot
our 50th Webcast of "iCarly"?
Insane.
We gotta make it, like,
our best show ever.
No doubt.
Hey, Jack, go long.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
"iCarly's" having a 50th
web show spectacular?
Yeah!
In five, four, three, two...
♪ I know you see ♪
♪ Somehow the world
will change for me ♪
♪ And be so wonderful ♪
♪ Live life, breathe air ♪
♪ I know somehow
we're going to get there ♪
♪ And feel so wonderful ♪
♪ It's all for real ♪
♪ I'm telling you
just how I feel ♪
♪ So wake up the members
of my nation ♪
♪ It's your time to breath ♪
♪ There's no chance
unless you take one ♪
♪ Every time you see
the brighter side ♪
♪ Of every situation ♪
♪ Some things
are meant to be ♪
♪ So give me your best
and leave the rest to me ♪
♪ Leave it all to me ♪
♪ Leave it all
to me ♪
♪ Just leave it all to me ♪
This girl is a menace.
I want her ess-pelled.
What?
He wants me expelled.
Mr. Howard, come on.
I realize it was wrong of Sam
to throw a football
in the hallway.
She almost killed me!
Yeah, almost.
I want something
done about this.
I understand, sort of.
Sam, you did break the rules,
so I'm going
to give you detention
with Mr. Howard tomorrow night.
Fine. I'll be there
tomorrow... wait.
I can't do it tomorrow night.
Why not?
Yeah. Why not?
I do a web show.
Oh, I know. "iCarly."
"iCarly"?
Yeah. Tomorrow night's
our 50th webcast
and it's gonna be, like,
a big thing, you know?
Yes?
Principal Franklin,
some ninth grade boys
are giving Gibby...
a Texas wedgie?
A Texas wedgie? All right.
Meet me there with a bag of ice
and a bottle of lotion.
Mr. Howard, you finish up here.
Wait. Just don't go...
You know,
I think you look better
with that thing on your face.
Be quiet.
Okay.
But can I please do
detention next week?
What, you think
just because
you're on a popular web show
that you deserve
some special treatment?
Yeah.
Well, tough kumquats.
Tough what?
Ow! Kumquats!
Ow!
Kumquats?
Why'd you have to get
detention tomorrow night?
Yeah, way to go, Sam.
You just ruined "iCarly" 's
50th web show spectac...
Ooh, popcorn.
You know, I read online that
popcorn's
one of the healthiest
snacks you can eat.
Yeah, I read that, too.
Whoa, whoa. What is that?
Two cups of melted butter.
Don't pour that
all over the popcorn.
It's full of fat and calories.
Okay.
Don't drink it.
So why don't you
just go talk to Mr. Howard
and explain that
it's "iCarly"'s 50...
Tried that. Didn't work.
Hey, what if we kidnap Howard
and keep him tied up
till after the show?
Okay, what have I told you
about kidnapping?
It's illegal and rude.
Good girl.
I'm home.
Where have you been?
Down at the golf course
getting golf balls
out of the big pond.
What for?
So I can sell 'em
and buy art supplies
for my next sculpture.
What are you making?
A gigantic coffee cup,
like 10 feet tall.
Why?
You know...
To symbolize the largeness
of some coffee cups.
They're big.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Have fun.
Happy shampoo.
Scrub it up.
So what do we do about "iCarly"?
We gotta figure a way
to get Sam out of detention.
Not gonna happen.
Mr. Howard hates my guts.
Maybe me and Carly need
to figure out a way
to get into detention.
Hey!
What?
"ICarly" live from detention.
Interesting.
Wait. You're serious?
Sure.
You and I do something bad,
we get detention,
then the three of us
will be together
to do the show.
How can we do the show
with Mr. Howard watching us
the whole time?
He hardly ever comes
in the room.
He always hangs
in the teacher's lounge
so he can watch
the geometry channel.
He's such a nub.
The nubbiest.
Okay, let's do it.
Awesome.
So tomorrow before school ends,
you and I have to get detention.
Yep.
You'll never guess
where I found this fish.
Hey.
Hello, Sam.
Why do you look all guilty?
I did something bad
to get detention.
What did you do?
You'll see.
All right, class,
everyone please sit.
Hey, Gibby, go ask
Mr. Palladino to staple
those together.
What for?
Shh! Just do it!
Go!
Hey, Mr. Palladino,
can you staple these papers
together?
Certainly, Gibby.
That's odd.
I don't see
the stapler anywhere.
I have it.
Wow. You are a maniac.
I'm sorry, Gibby.
I can't find the stapler.
That's right, 'cause I took it.
Ah, yes.
Thank you, Freddie.
There you are, Gibby.
Here.
Keep 'em.
All right, kids.
The sooner we start,
the sooner we finish.
So everybody,
let's take your seats.
Aah!
What happened to my chair?
I did it with whatever this is.
Do I get detention?
Absolutely not.
An on-the-job accident means
the school has to give me
a two-month paid vacation
while I recover.
Bye!
Dude, this is the principal's
office.
I know. I'm so bad.
Look what I did.
Freddie says principal
Franklin...
Sucks eggs.
Impressive. That might
get you double detention.
Yep. When principal
Franklin sees that,
you better believe he's gonna...
Come on, Carly.
It's for the 50th web show
spectacular.
You can do this.
Who pulled that fire alarm?
It was me.
Thank goodness you did.
The microwave
in the teacher's lounge
just burst into flames.
Out of the way! Out of the way!
Ow, ow, ow! Out of the way!
Who knew getting in trouble
would be so impossible.
I gotta give you credit, Sam.
You make it look easy.
Years of practice.
Hey, thanks for that fire alarm.
You saved me from giving
an oral report
on "Scarlett's Web."
You were too lazy
to read the book?
I was too lazy to see the movie.
Well, now what?
We're supposed to do
the 50th webcast of "iCarly"
from detention in five hours
and Sam's the only one
that's gonna be there.
Why is it so hard
to get detention?
Who slammed that locker?
Me.
Detention!
Really?
Tonight!
Yay!
Yay?
Darn.
You did it.
Yeah, but we still
need our tech producer
and school's over
in three minutes.
How am I gonna get detention
in three minutes?
You better,
or else no show tonight.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Wait here.
I don't mind stopping
by Crusty Creme.
I...
You heard I got
the new pear phone.
Yep, these babies
are indestructible.
Hello, honey. I'm back.
Yes, I will pick up the donuts.
Mm-hmm.
Aw, man, school's over.
And you didn't get detention.
Which means no "iCarly"
50th web show spectacular.
It couldn't be worse.
Yes, it could.
How?
We could be Gibby.
They gave me
another Texas wedgie.
Man,
when Spencer said
he was building
a gigantic cup of coffee,
he wasn't kidding around.
Where is Spencer?
Hey, Spencer!
I'm here.
Is that thing filled
with coffee?
Just about 500 gallons.
Spencer, that's crazy.
It's okay. It's decaf.
Okay, but why are you in there?
'Cause after I filled it
with coffee,
I dropped my cell phone in here.
Been trying to find it
for the past two hours.
Wish me luck.
Hey, I figured out a way for us
to do "iCarly" tonight.
Is that a 10 foot tall
coffee cup?
10'2".
I'm not gonna ask.
Just tell us how we're gonna do
the show tonight.
All right. Is there a closet
in the classroom?
Yeah.
Good.
And you guys can hide
my tech equipment in there
so Mr. Howard won't see it.
Yeah, but what about you?
You can't be in there
unless you have detention.
You said he's almost never
in the room
'cause he's watching
the geometry channel
in the teacher's lounge, right?
Yeah.
So as soon as he checks roll
and leaves,
you guys give me a signal
and I'll sneak in the window.
But the classroom's
on the second floor.
You can borrow my ladder.
Awesome.
Did I hear you say
you got detention?
Yeah.
Should I be concerned?
Not really.
Later.
Now, you are all here
because you are the worst
this school has to offer.
I am here because I believe
in punishment and discipline
and I hate you all.
All right.
I will be down the hall
in the teacher's lounge
watching the geometry channel.
While I am gone,
there is to be no talking.
I hope you have a terrible time.
We're good now
for at least 10 minutes.
Let's go.
Okay, everybody.
We're about to start
the 50th webcast of "iCarly."
You guys into it?
Yeah.
Totally.
Okay, wants to be the lookout
in case Mr. Howard came back?
I'll do it.
Hey.
Go signal Freddie.
Right.
Ca-caw, ca-caw!
Ca-caw.
Do it like a bird.
Ca-caw!
Carly, what's the signal
for Mr. Howard's coming?
Dippity-doo.
Everybody sit down.
Pull me in!
Too late.
Don't... aww.
I heard noise.
What's going on?
Nothing.
We're just sitting here
having a terrible time.
Oh, good.
Just sit here and don't move.
I'll get the stuff
out of the closet.
I'll get Freddie.
Ca-caw.
Here. You wear the cap-cam.
Why?
There's a camera in it.
If jerk-face comes back,
Freddie hides in the closet
and we switch out "iCarly"
to the hidden camera
in your hat.
Cool.
I fell on a shrub.
Coast clear?
All clear.
Then we are live on the web
in 5, 4, 3, 2...
Why did we scream?
Because...
It's "iCarly"'s 50th web show
spectacular.
It's true.
This is the 50th webcast
of "iCarly."
And it is spectacular.
Spectacular.
I'm Carly...
And I'm Sam...
And maybe you've noticed...
This isn't our usual
"iCarly" studio.
And if you haven't noticed...
Scrape that crud
out of your eyes.
We're webcasting to you
live from our school.
Room 29...
Because we got...
Detention.
Tell 'em why we got detention.
'Cause we're naughty.
Dippity-doo!
Okay.
You just heard our friend
Claire yell dippity-doo.
Which means that
our horrible teacher
Mr. Howard is coming.
I gotta hide.
Freddie's gonna hide
in the closet.
And we're switching
to the cap-cam
in our friend Billy's hat.
Switching to the cap-cam.
I have ears like a hawk.
I distinctly heard laughter
and I hate laughter.
I thought you hated your wife.
Her, too.
Now keep your mouths shut.
Isn't he charming?
Freddie, let's go.
Switching back to the main cam.
Okay. We were talking
about the things
kids do that get 'em detention.
Why, look.
Here's a gold member
of the detention club
right here.
It's ninth grader
Rip Off Rodney.
Please, call me Rip Off.
So how'd you get detention?
Selling fake hall passes.
Nice.
And how'd you get caught?
I, uh... I misspelled "hall."
Two Ls.
Yeah.
Okay, so you got anything else
to say to the "iCarly" fans
of the world?
Yeah. I got a special
this week on burritos.
Two for six bucks.
And do they contain
quality meat?
No, they do not.
And now continuing
with our game of hangman...
JD, it's your turn to guess
a letter or solve the puzzle.
All right, is it...
Mr. Howard eats pants?
Correct!
He certainly does.
Okay. H-o-t...
Dippity-doo!
Everybody hide!
Switching to the cap-cam.
Uh-huh.
Everybody's so innocent.
Do I smell burritos?
I have a feeling...
Who wrote this?
Who wrote this lie?
Never in my entire life
have I eaten one pair of pants.
Somebody gonna confess,
or do you all wanna do
200 push-ups?
Principal Franklin says
you can't give physical
punishment in detention.
Principal Franklin.
If you ask me,
he's not even fit
to be in charge of this school.
He's weak. Spineless.
Well, I think
I'm just gonna sit here
and stare at you gutter children
until detention is over.
And I think
I'll add an extra two hours.
Just hang on.
Freddie has a way to get rid
of Mr. Howard.
Hey, no talking
to that boy's hat.
Wesley, now.
Check.
What in tarnation?
What is that?
Stay here and say nothing.
Switching back to the main cam.
Okay, now that dippity-doo
done gone...
Next on "iCarly"...
Live from detention...
Turtle races!
Come on, give him a kiss.
Kiss him, kiss him.
Mine wants a big kiss.
Come on, you can do it.
Hey! You there!
Stop! Who are you?
Stop, you hooligan!
Remove your sack.
Hey!
Yoo-ie, yoo-ie,
yoo-ie, yoo-ie, yoo-ie, yoo-ie.
We gotta go.
Who says slow can't be exciting?
You can only get this stuff
at iCarly.com, baby.
Ha!
A video camera? Turtles?
Burritos?
What is going on in here?
The "iCarly" 50th web show
spectacular?
You're all really
in trouble now.
I am talking suspension.
I am talking expulsion.
Deportation.
And you can all start
with 500 push-ups.
I don't care
what Principal Franklin
has to say about it.
You don't?
No! I... oh, dear.
Principal Franklin.
What are you doing here?
Well, I was at home,
watching the "iCarly"
50th web show spectacular.
Congratulations, by the way.
My kids and I love your show.
Wow.
Awesome.
While I was watching,
I heard Mr. Howard
call me a weak, spineless fool.
No, no, no! I said...
Uh, sweet. Stylish.
Cool.
In my office.
But I...
Now.
Why does everything
always happen to me?
So now what?
Well, I suppose Mr. Howard
has tortured you all enough.
Go home.
Okay, we're just about done.
I'm Sam...
I'm Carly...
And I'm Ted.
And thanks for watching
the "iCarly" 50th web show
spectacular.
May I?
Second button from the bottom.
It's "iCarly"'s 50th web show
spectacular.
Bye! Keep clicking
iCarly.com. Don't forget it.
And we're clear.
Yeah!
Whoo!
How fun is this?
It's like a java-cuzzi.
Hey!
Who wants more coffee?
I do!
Whoo!
Yeah!
This isn't weird at all.
Hi, Carly. Hi, Sam.
Watch what I can do.
"ICarly" rocks.